# Vladislav Plyushchenko

Phone: +44 7756 808372 · Email: vladplyu@gmail.com · DOB: 09/19/2005

Personal Website: vladapl21.github.io · LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/vladplyushchenko · GitHub: vladapl21

#### **PROFILE**

I am a London A-Level student with a background in business and technology. Currently, I am researching innovation in the data management and privacy sector. This upcoming year, I will be moving to the US for university. Besides technological entrepreneurship, I also have an inclination towards environmental preservation, always considering this growing field when coming up with solutions to modern problems.

## **SKILLS**

MS Excel / Google Sheets Website Development Microsoft Office Data Analysis
Presentation Creation & Delivery
Communication Skills

Languages
Fluent: English, Russian
Proficient: Spanish, French

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Andurance Ventures LLP**

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

## **Business Analyst / Technical Project Management Intern**

Created reusable <u>Excel Model</u> that company used to decide if they should outsource or hire directly for various tasks. Tackled scaling problems with NovaQuark branch of the firm by designing them a novel knowledge management architecture. Optimized one of their commodity algo-traders by suggesting the use of an alternate data structure.

Harrow Hemp Co. Sep 2022 - Jan 2023

#### **Sustainable School Uniform Business**

Prototyped and presented business idea at <u>Makyth Ventures 2022</u> with over 200 participants. Idea won overall prize as seen on their <u>LinkedIn page</u>. Created information <u>poster</u> and co-created <u>presentation</u>.

GreenEnterprise Sep 2023 - Present

# Founded International Sustainable Entrepreneurship Competition

1000+ participants from over 20 International schools asked to create an elevator pitch on an idea that has a component of sustainability. Co-created comp. <u>website</u> on Vue. Created and <u>presented</u> comp. to 800+.

## **EDUCATION**

## Harrow School, UK, 2019 - Present

(I)GCSEs: 10x Grade 9, 1x Grade 8, 1x Grade 7 AS Achieved: Computer Science (A - max. grade)

A-Level Achieved: Russian (A\*)

A-Level Predicted: Computer Science (A\*), Economics (A\*), Physics (A\*), Mathematics (A\*)

Newton Preparatory School, UK, 2013 - 2019 International School of Moscow, 2008 - 2013

## **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

Secretary, School Economics / Business Society Harrow School

**Digital Operations Manager Volunteer**Open Culture Foundation Charity

Founder of \$12k Music Marketing Business

Plu.ru